<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data>
        <template id="tmp_odoo_implementation" name="Odoo Implementation">
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <section>
                    <div class="container-fluid" style="padding: 0;">
                        <img src="/kanak_website/static/src/img/odoo_implementation/Bg_banner.png" class="img-responsive center-block" />
                        <!-- <div class="col-lg-6 col-md-6 col-sm-4 col-xs-12 overlay" style="position: absolute; top: 40pt">
                            <h2>Odoo Customization &amp; Implementation</h2>
                        </div> -->
                    </div>
                </section>
                <section>
                    <!-- <div id="odoo_img" class="container-fluid" style="padding: 10pt 10pt 0 0">
                        <img src="/kanak_website/static/src/img/odoo_implementation/Odoo.png" class="img-responsive" />
                    </div> -->
                    <div class="container">
                        <div class="col-lg-12">
                            <h1 class="text-uppercase" style="font-size:28px;font-weight: 900;color: #003362;">Odoo Customization and <span class="orange">Implementation</span></h1>
                            <p>Odoo Open source <a href="/odoo-development-services">Odoo Open Source ERP</a> is a framework which lead off an enterprise's real growth potential by simplifying operational challenges and streamlining business workflows. Being an <a href="https://kanakinfosystems.com/blog/best-mobile-app-development-software">open source framework</a>, it is very cost-effective open source and used by many users without any difficulty. And also, it does not need any license to use. This is very flexible to use as this is a modular software which entitle enterprises to add or delete modules as per project needs.</p>
                            <p>Our Odoo ERP system are specifically tailored and customized for the requirement of your industry, it not only addresses the current requirements of your company but it also provides you with the opportunity of continually improving and refining your business processes.</p>
                            <p>Most organizations across the world have realized that in a rapidly changing environment, it is impossible to create and maintain a pure custom designed software package which will cater to all their requirements and also be completely up-to-date.</p>
                            <p>Realizing this requirement of many organizations <a href="https://kanakinfosystems.com">Kanak Infoystems</a> offers its Enterprise Resource Planning software which will offer an <a href="https://kanakinfosystems.com/contact-us">integrated software solution</a> to all the functions of an organization.</p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </section>
                <section style="background-color: #fbfbfb">
                    <div class="container">
                        <h2 class="text-uppercase text-center">Odoo ERP Customization <br /><span class="orange">Follows Steps</span></h2>
                        <div id="follow_step" class="col-lg-12 col-md-12">
                            
                            <div class="col-lg-6 col-md-6">
                                <div>
                                    <h2><span class="orange" style="font-size:20px;">&amp;mdash;</span> Requirement Analysis </h2>
                                    <p>In general, this step includes understanding the client’s expectations from the required customization and striving to ensure that the Odoo customization is done efficiently to meet those requirements.</p>
                                </div>
                                <div>
                                    <h2><span class="orange" style="font-size:20px;">&amp;mdash;</span> Prioritize Business Requirements </h2>
                                    <p>Prioritization is an essential step, which is usually based on the mission-critical issues of the business organization. It helps focus on the key requirements to be addressed via Odoo Customization.</p>
                                </div>
                                <div>
                                    <h2><span class="orange" style="font-size:20px;">&amp;mdash;</span> Process Mapping </h2>
                                    <p>For faster delivery of processes and to identify bottlenecks, repetitions, and delays, we undertake process mapping. This helps us define process boundaries, process ownership, process responsibilities, and metrics.</p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-lg-6 col-md-6">

                                <div>
                                    <h2><span class="orange" style="font-size:20px;">&amp;mdash;</span> GAP Analysis</h2>
                                    <p>In this step, service providers and business personnel sit together to analyze the current scenario, expectations, and the gap. Then, it involves describing that gap with the best possible Odoo customization services based on the service provider’s potential and resources.</p>
                                </div>
                                <div>
                                    <h2><span class="orange" style="font-size:20px;">&amp;mdash;</span> Spot Existing Apps</h2>
                                    <p>This phase includes identifying if the customization can be managed completely or partially through existing <a href="https://kanakinfosystems.com/shop">Odoo applications</a>.</p>
                                </div>
                                <div>
                                    <h2><span class="orange" style="font-size:20px;">&amp;mdash;</span> Customization</h2>
                                    <p>As an acclaimed Odoo Customization Company, we believe in a proven methodology for all our Odoo customization projects. Daily and weekly planning of tasks, progress control, and re-evaluation are some of the essential processes to ensure robust customization.</p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-lg-6 col-lg-offset-3 col-md-6 col-md-offset-3 text-center">
                                <div>
                                    <h2><span class="orange" style="font-size:20px;">&amp;mdash;</span> Testing and Go-live <span class="text-danger" style="color: red;font-size:20px;">&amp;mdash;</span></h2>
                                    <p class="text-center">By testing our experts carry out to ensure that the custom development works as intended and goes smooth without interrupting anything else in the software. After everything is tested, the system will Go-Live.</p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </section>
                <section>
                    <div class="container">
                        <div class="col-lg-10 col-lg-offset-1 text-center">
                            <h2 class="text-uppercase">Odoo Implementation</h2>
                            <p class="text-center">For an efficient <a href="https://kanakinfosystems.com/blog/factors-for-successful-erp-implementation">ERP implementation</a>, choosing the right technology with thorough documentation, commitment from stakeholders, effective communication, employee training is a must go.</p>
                            <p class="text-center">Here, Odoo steps in to provide everything to implement robust business solutions, right from higher productivity to more data security and cost savings resources.</p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </section>
                <section>
                    <div class="container">
                        <div id="odoo_includes" class="col-lg-12">
                            <h3 class="text-uppercase" style="font-size:28px;font-weight: 900;color: #003362;">Odoo Delivers a Process-driven Approach that <span class="red">includes:</span></h3>
                            <div>
                                <h2><span style="background-image: url(/kanak_website/static/src/img/odoo_implementation/Arrow.png); background-repeat: no-repeat; background-size: 16px; background-position: center;" >&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</span>Involvement At Every Step  <span class="orange" style="font-size:20px;">&amp;mdash;</span></h2>
                                <p>Particularly, the team of experts in the field understands the value of developing, testing, and delivering <a href="https://kanakinfosystems.com/erp-solutions">ERP solutions</a>. We involve business administrators and make them an integral part of the process to let them orient and guide the team towards meeting the organizational goals.</p>
                            </div>
                            <div>
                                <h2><span style="background-image: url(/kanak_website/static/src/img/odoo_implementation/Arrow.png); background-repeat: no-repeat; background-size: 16px; background-position: center;" >&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</span>Slick Transition  <span class="orange" style="font-size:20px;">&amp;mdash;</span></h2>
                                <p>In general, an acclaimed Odoo ERP implementation company keeps its focus to grasp and understand the various decisions taken through configuration and customization. Also, constant feedbacks from the stakeholders helps the service providers identify any gaps in the solutions as well.</p>
                                <p>Once done, we lead the client’s team through a series of demonstrations and support by providing necessary documentation for a smooth transition.</p>
                            </div>
                            <div>
                                <h2><span style="background-image: url(/kanak_website/static/src/img/odoo_implementation/Arrow.png); background-repeat: no-repeat; background-size: 16px; background-position: center;" >&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</span>Planning  <span class="orange" style="font-size:20px;">&amp;mdash;</span></h2>
                                <p>We understand the significance of proper planning when it comes to Odoo implementation. It shows great results when the execution phase arrives and that time consumption turns out to be judiciously beneficial.</p>
                                <p>Also, we follow a robust methodology for planning projects as a solution provider that reflects our client’s objectives and expectations. Moreover, ensuring that each member from the team is chosen based on their core areas of expertise helps us use the abilities to build a strong solution driver greater value and profitability.</p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </section>
                <section>
                    <div class="container">
                        <div id="odoo_services" class="col-lg-12 col-md-12">
                            <h3 class="text-uppercase text-center" style="font-size:28px;font-weight: 900;color: #003362;">A Brief on Our Odoo ERP Development <br /><span class="red">Services</span></h3>
                            <img src="/kanak_website/static/src/img/odoo_implementation/Down_arrow.png" class="center-block"/>
                            <div class="col-lg-4 col-md-4">
                                <div class="text-center">
                                    <img src="/kanak_website/static/src/img/odoo_implementation/Odoo_Customization.png" class="center-block"/>
                                    <h2>Odoo Customization</h2>
                                    <p class="text-center">We will fullfill your business Needs with our expertise!</p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-lg-4 col-md-4">
                                <div class="text-center">
                                    <img src="/kanak_website/static/src/img/odoo_implementation/Odoo_Implementation.png"  class="center-block"/>
                                    <h2>Odoo Implementation</h2>
                                    <p class="text-center">We understand your businessRequirements! We customize the eachEach module to implement it in the wayyou want!</p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-lg-4 col-md-4">
                                <div class="text-center">
                                    <img src="/kanak_website/static/src/img/odoo_implementation/Odoo_Training.png"  class="center-block"/>
                                    <h2><a href="https://kanakinfosystems.com/odoo-training" >Odoo Training</a></h2>
                                    <p class="text-center">We provide Advance Technical and Functional training by our experts!</p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-lg-4 col-md-4">
                                <div class="text-center">
                                    <img src="/kanak_website/static/src/img/odoo_implementation/Odoo_Integration.png"  class="center-block"/>
                                    <h2><a href="https://kanakinfosystems.com/odoo-integration-services">Odoo Integration</a></h2>
                                    <p class="text-center">We offer out of the box solution to Integrate Odoo with 3rd party application!</p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-lg-4 col-md-4">
                                <div class="text-center">
                                    <img src="/kanak_website/static/src/img/odoo_implementation/Odoo_Migration.png"  class="center-block"/>
                                    <h2>Odoo Migration</h2>
                                    <p class="text-center">We provide data and code Migrationfrom your legacy system!</p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-lg-4 col-md-4">
                                <div class="text-center">
                                    <img src="/kanak_website/static/src/img/odoo_implementation/Odoo_Support_and_Maintenance.png" class="center-block"/>
                                    <h2>Odoo Support and Maintenance</h2>
                                    <p class="text-center">We provide 24 X7 bug fixes and issue Resolving and version upgrade!</p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </section>
                <section>
                    <div class="col-lg-4 col-lg-offset-4 col-md-6 col-md-offset-3 "> <div id="odoo_feature" class="text-uppercase text-white text-center">Odoo Features</div></div>
                    <div class="container" style="padding: 40pt;">
                        <img src="/kanak_website/static/src/img/odoo_implementation/Odoo_Features.png" class="img-responsive center-block" />
                        
                    </div>
                </section>
                <section>
                    <div class="container">
                        <div class="faq_border" style="border: 1px solid #cec7c7;">
                            <br />
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-lg-3 col-md-3 col-sm-3">
                                    <div class="frequently_border_1" />
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-lg-6 col-md-4 col-sm-6">
                                    <h2 class="fw700 text-center">
                                        <font style="font-size: 30px;text-transform: uppercase;">
                                            <span class="dark_blue">frequently asked questions</span>
                                        </font>
                                    </h2>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-lg-3 col-md-3 col-sm-3">
                                    <div class="frequently_border_2" />
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <br /><br /><br />
                            <div class="row faq_box" style="padding: 80px;margin-top: -100px;margin-bottom: -30px;">
                                <div>
                                    <img id="faq_icon_1" class="faq_button_1 faq_button" src="/kanak_website/static/src/img/netsuite_page/drop_down.png" /><strong style="color: #003362;margin-left: 10px;font-size: 19px;">1. Why I Choose Partners Over Freelancers For Odoo Customization?</strong>
                                    <div id="faq_1" style="display:none;">
                                        <p style="margin-top: 20px;margin-left: 40px;">An official <a href="https://www.odoo.com/partners/kanak-infosystems-llp-19492?country_id=101">Odoo partner</a> is exclusively specialized on keys like Odoo Consultancy, Odoo implementation, Odoo Customization, and Odoo Training as well. Moreover, these partners have authorized signatories having access to Enterprise Edition source code to provide quick resolutions to issues. Furthermore, one can avail of tailor-made solutions ensuring guaranteed delivery.</p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <br />
                                <div>
                                    <img class="faq_button faq_button_2" id="faq_icon_2" src="/kanak_website/static/src/img/netsuite_page/drop_down.png" />
                                    <strong style="color: #003362;margin-left: 10px;font-size: 19px;">2. Why Kanakinfosystems For Odoo Customization?</strong>
                                    <div id="faq_2" style="display:none;">
                                        <p style="margin-top: 20px;margin-left: 40px;">Odoo customization solutions deliver a 360-degree view for managing and organizing the entire business operations efficiently. We provide extensive and guaranteed delivery of services in <a href="https://kanakinfosystems.com/odoo-installation-services">Odoo installation</a>, implementation of customized modules, post-implementation support. It helps businesses conduct grass-root level business analysis to understand business workflows and needs.</p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <br />
                                <div>
                                    <img class="faq_button faq_button_3" id="faq_icon_3" src="/kanak_website/static/src/img/netsuite_page/drop_down.png" />
                                    <strong style="color: #003362;margin-left: 10px;font-size: 19px;">3. How A Reliable Partner Can Fulfill Your Customization-Oriented Business Goals?</strong>
                                    <div id="faq_3" style="display:none;">
                                        <p style="margin-top: 20px;margin-left: 40px;">Connecting with an astute service provider partner can help ensure the functionality that fits in the business. Also, they are committed to taking care of business requirements and business workflow while implementing the customization. Furthermore, they ensure robust and highly scalable customizations to meet specific business needs.</p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <br />
                                <div>
                                    <img class="faq_button faq_button_4" id="faq_icon_4" src="/kanak_website/static/src/img/netsuite_page/drop_down.png" />
                                    <strong style="color: #003362;margin-left: 10px;font-size: 19px;">4. How much does Odoo’s implementation cost?</strong>
                                    <div id="faq_4" style="display:none;">
                                        <p style="margin-top: 20px;margin-left: 40px;">It largely depends on the size of the business organization, including small, medium-sized, and large enterprises. Usually, it covers software license, number of users, renewal fees, training, customization, functionality, maintenance &amp; upgrades.</p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <br/>
                                <div>
                                    <img class="faq_button faq_button_5" id="faq_icon_5" src="/kanak_website/static/src/img/netsuite_page/drop_down.png" />
                                    <strong style="color: #003362;margin-left: 10px;font-size: 19px;">5. How can I pick the best Odoo Implementation Partner?</strong>
                                    <div id="faq_5" style="display:none;">
                                        <p style="margin-top: 20px;margin-left: 40px;">You should choose a partner holding an impressive and successful history of Odoo ERP implementations. Partners deploying the right resources, a unique approach, and industry-leading practices for such an implementation can be your preferred choice.</p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </section><br />
            </t>
        </template>
    </data>
</odoo>